What a big fish.
I hope I didn't crush it to death.
How can water grab people?
It's hard.
It's warm.
These are...
pecs.
I didn't mean to.
The water started it.
Who are you?
Let me go!
Li.
Is it you?
I don't know you.
You are not her.
Am I going to die?
But I don't even
remember who I am.
Don't be afraid.
Follow the bell
and go home.
Go home?
Where is my home?
Master, bad news!
There's a telepathic message.
Sorry, Master.
I didn't know you were...
What happened?
Speak.
The divine beast suddenly woke up.
Help me take her and Bai back.
For thousands of years,
the Master has never shown
interest in women.
Today he actually took the initiative
to get close.
Is the old iron tree finally blooming?
Master, you're back.
Where is that girl?
In your room.
She's probably not up yet.
Ye Qifeng,
you've got some nerve, haven't you?
How dare you send just anyone to my room?
Oh no.
I think I misunderstood.
Does the Master like wild...
Swallow those two words in your heart.
Master,
you read my mind again.
It's written all over your face.
You definitely read it.
Master,
I've already checked.
She's just a mortal.
But last night the Eye of Gods
and Demons was opened,
the divine beast awakened,
and a mortal fell from the sky.
Bai was injured again.
Do you think she could be a spy
from the Demonic Cult?
Uncle,
if there is a next life,
I will be your wife again.
Li.
Could it be you?
I don't know where I am,
but this food is amazing.
I'll eat first.
I need a full stomach
to figure out how to escape.
It's the guy with the hard pecs
from last night.
No.
It's the guy
who almost choked me to death.
Is he going to make me pay
for that fish with my life?
No way.
I have to find a way to escape.